In revenge, patience is a virtue. And after a thousand years,
Colin MacLeod doesn't give a damn about virtue ...
Highlander: The Search for Vengeance is a action, animation,
fantasy film directed by Yoshiaki Kawajiri.
Colin MacLeod hunts for the man responsible for the death of his love.
He chases the immortal Marcus Octavius across centuries as his
quest threatens to take over his life and heart.
In his quest, he meets a woman who reminds him of his slain beauty.
But it's his final battle with Marcus that will decide not only his
fate, but also the fate of everyone in the world.
Colin MacLeod (voice), played by Alistair Abell.
Dahlia (voice), played by Debi Mae West.
Marcus Octavius (voice), played by Nolan North.
Amergan / Gregor / Lad Director (voice), played by Scott McNeil.
Joe (voice), played by Ogie Banks.
Kyala (voice), played by Janyse Jaud.
Highlander: The Search for Vengeance is a 2007 adult animated dystopian fantasy
action film and an anime installment in the Highlander franchise.
The film was directed by Yoshiaki Kawajiri (Ninja Scroll, Vampire Hunter D: Bloodlust) and was written by David
Abramowitz, also the writer for Highlander: The Series, Highlander: The Raven and Highlander: The Source.
The film was a joint venture between Imagi Animation Studios and Madhouse Studio, with Imagi
providing the script and the soundtrack, while Madhouse produced the animation.
It was produced in association with Davis-Panzer Productions and distributed by Manga
Entertainment on June 5, 2007 and aired on July 30 on Sci Fi's Ani-Monday block.
The film is dedicated to the memory of William N.
Panzer, who died in 2007, and was the co-owner of Davis-Panzer Productions.
The film explores themes of future, new love, immortality, highlander, revenge.
The tone is thought_provoking.